If I can be honest with myself, not appreciating or valuing what was important to her enough
in the moment. I think I wasn't, yeah, I'm like, oh, okay. You know what I'm saying? Like,
I get it, but do what I want to do. You're a dark cloud. Like, why are you waiting on my parade?
Just jump with me, baby. Jump with me. So. Not realizing that she was jumping with you.
She was in her way. It's just that you were, she was turning. Yes.
The turner got to be solid. Come on. A thousand percent.
The ground got to be solid. You can't jump.
I can't be doing this. You're jumping though. Jump. Yeah. Turn. Yeah. I see you.
I wasn't valuing that enough. Over the years, I've learned that it's balanced. Sometimes it's more me,
sometimes it's more her. Absolutely. But I say this to her on calls or after calls all the time.
At our worst, if we agree with you, the worst case scenario is our money safe.
If we listen to me, our worst case scenario, our money not safe.